what is the schedule I know you want to
know the schedule changes all the time
so here's the
latest uh we are going to increase the
copy boost in the morning to 90 minutes
uh so there's more time to take your
questions uh just an invitation to
anyone who has technical questions or
questions about anything but
particularly technical questions the
coffee boost was primarily added to help
you out so that we can keep you going um
and if maybe you know you have a
question about something that hasn't
covered in a video maybe we'll even make
the video right away right there so the
coffee boost please come in uh the other
important change is the beginner boost
is 10 to 2 p.m. so that's that's like 1
two 3 4 hours long it is pretty long and
I admit I I take you know breaks in
there and stuff because that is a lot of
time to go without eating or anything um
but you know it is what it is um perhaps
someday we'll be able to uh reduce the
time for the beginner to boost on
Saturday uh once we have all the videos
uh queued up and that's probably a year
away so not going to be doing that other
changes to the calendar that are more
relevant to people who watch me for IRL
um we'll be doing IRL yoga every day at
4:30 to 6 not we I am I am committing to
myself to do yoga every day from for 90
minutes that's 90 minutes of asanga yoga
uh I'm doing my own modified inspired by
asanga uh
you know set of poses which I will
publish uh so those of you who want to
know the poses I do um that's going to
be from David Swanson's book um uh and
you know it's it's it's pretty cringey
because it's you know me doing yoga um
and but if you but if you want to join
us it's just music and yoga um if you
want to allocate that time for your own
practice um love to have you uh again
I'm not going to be talking at all
during this time that is completely
muted um there's no nothing that's just
me doing yoga from a reasonable
distance at a beautiful location
someplace um so the next thing after
that I found out is kind of nice is um
doing the bike trips the bike rides
after yoga now those of you who know me
know that I am now
doing um uh
what I call gravel plus
cycling so I do not I'm I'm going to be
on sometimes I'll be on a mountain bike
trail sometimes I'm going to be on the
road sometimes I'm going to be going
just exploring random suburbs or random
locations or random you know uh back
woodsy areas I there's really no plan I
just get on the bike and go um there is
a preferred route that I generally do a
couple of that I that I do but but I'm
not even promising that I will be on
those every time so um and this is
important that I talk about this so so
you can see the the calendar is is is
pretty standard I obviously I work in
between here uh we are talking about
possibly adding co-working back and when
putting some music in the middle here
I've been accused of being quote
sloppy uh by doing co-working U but
there's been an overwhelming demand to
add it back so that might come back but
I'm not going to promise that right now
um one thing to keep in mind this
particular schedule is so that we can do
the same schedule on the road um in July
I'm still set to be doing a road trip
and it's a very important part of the
road trip to not
be uh impacted by the fact that I'm
living out of my car I still want to be
able to maintain my yoga I still want to
be able to maintain my fitness with my
bike and for that reason the schedule
that you see here is designed to be
sustainable by living from a car so
crossing the country and that is why for
example where did the paddle boarding go
that paddle boarding is gone from that
schedule now uh I might do it on
occasion but it's not going to be in the
regular schedule um it's the reason that
I've pushed so far back on the times
down to 5 4:30 because we'll be doing
you know my job during the other part of
the day um and that that is really the
reason we want to keep it something
sustainable so if you'd like to join me
uh there it is that's the latest it's
going to change it always does